{
    "subject": "resource/Israel_Ledesma_Maga\u00f1a",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Mexico",
    "human_readable": "Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a was born in Mexico.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9624994397163391,
            "question": "Is Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a Mexican?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9585143327713013,
            "question": "Where was Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9040887951850891,
            "question": "What is the name of the country where Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145045042037964,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7768457531929016,
            "question": "What country is Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.764934778213501,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6820976734161377,
            "question": "What is known about Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6036396026611328,
            "question": "In which nation did Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5222277045249939,
            "question": "Where did Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a spend his early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44281744956970215,
            "question": "Mexico is the birthplace of whom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a was born in Mexico.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3283_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a spend his early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3283_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which nation did Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3283_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3283_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3283_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can answer:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the document mentions that \"In this Spanish name, the first or paternalsurname is Ledesma and the second or maternal family name is Maga\u00f1a.\" which suggests that Israel Reyes Ledesma Maga\u00f1a has both a paternal surname (Ledesma) and a maternal surname (Maga\u00f1a). Additionally, his full birthdate (16 May 1954) and place of death (Mexican Congress representing the State of Mexico) are mentioned, implying that he was born in Mexico."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The context information provided includes a biographical entry for Israel Reyes Ledesma Maga\u00f1a, which mentions that he was a Mexican politician and that the date of his birth is given as 16 May 1954. This supports the statement that Israel Ledesma Maga\u00f1a was born in Mexico."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There are multiple entries about Mexican people, but none of them mention Israel Reyes Ledesma Maga\u00f1a.  He also appears to be a politician and was involved with the Mexican Congress.  \n\n\n\nLet me know if you have any other questions!",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}